<TextList>
	<Text id="intro">
		Long ago, the Holy Empire of Constantia existed in the balance of two religions.
		The cult of Vetus, preaching the value of keeping things constant and unchanged
		and the cult of Novum, whose followers were always seeking innovations and
		change. The two beliefs always coexisted together, complementing each other
		until one day...
		The cult of Novum's thirst for change quickly escalated, the balance between the
		two cults was disrupted and thus began the first civil war in the Constantia
		Empire's history. The cult of Vetus emerged victorious and to ensure peace and
		order would be preserved within the Empire, they exiled any remaining followers
		of Novum on a remote island, one of the Empire's newly acquired colony.
		For the following years, peace remained in the Empire. However, the Empire
		received a few months ago reports claiming that members of the cult of Novum
		have been gathering, rumors saying they are trying to take over the colony and
		rebel against the Empire. No words from the colony ever since. In order to
		investigate in this matter, the Empire sent a young hero on the island.
		This is where the story begins.
		The future depends on this young man's actions...
	</Text>
  <Text id="AncoraIntro">
		The ship docked at Ancora Port. After weeks of sailing the sea, the hero
		finally reached the colony. This town seemed peaceful, but the hero knew his
		journey would be dangerous and filled with battles. In order to make up for
		those weeks at sea, the hero decided to spar with some of his soldiers.
  </Text>
  <Text id="AncoraEnd">
		As expected, our hero emerged victorious of this sparring session. He *IS* the
		hero after all! The hero asked the town locale regarding the cult of Novum's 
		recent actions. The people didn't know much since this is a remote town. They
		advised our young hero to go to the city of Serena, to the East.
		
		There are two ways to reach Serena. Head north to the Glarea Peaks or south in
		the Dusty Woods.
		
		Two paths, two destinies. What will our hero choose...
  </Text>
  <Text id="Glarea PeaksIntro">
		In order to reach the city of Serena, our young hero decided to make his way
		through the Glarea Peaks. Upon reaching the Glarea Outpost, the scouts spot a
		group of bandits about to raid a nearby village.
		
		"To arms, comrades! We must defend the village!"
		
		The hero's army rode to battle.
  </Text>
  <Text id="Glarea PeaksEnd">
		The ruffians were slain to the last, the village was saved. The villagers were
		greatful for the hero's help. 
		
		"Bandits raiding villages... it's as if the Empire doesn't care one bit about
		the colony's well being. Some of those people are trying their best to live a
		fair life despite of their people's actions in the past. I believe one should be
		allowed to live by his own beliefs."
		
		The hero continued his journey, it wasn't just the Empire now, the colony's
		people depended on him too.
  </Text>
  <Text id="Dusty WoodsIntro">
		To reach the city of Serena, the hero chose to journey through the Dusty Woods.
		As his troops were walking through the woods, the hero heard daunting chants
		and smell of burning trees reached his nose.
		
		"Whoever those people are, they're up to no good. We must stop them!"
  </Text>
  <Text id="Dusty WoodsEnd">
		The mysterious fellows have been defeated and the forest was saved. The hero
		learned from people living in Dusty village that they were from the cult of
		Novum.
		
		"Those Novum fellows sure don't seem like the friendliest people around. No
		wonder the Empire sent me to investigate things here."
		
		The hero pressed on towards Serena.
  </Text>
  <Text id="SerenaIntro">
		Upon reaching Serena, the young hero couldn't be more surprised. The city was
		being attacked. They were informed by a fleeing villager that it was the cult of
		Novum attacking. They had grown in power ever since the last few months and
		progressively took over the whole colony.
		
		"No time to waste! We must reclaim the city of Serena!"
  </Text>
  <Text id="SerenaEnd">
		The city was saved from the cult of Novum. Why did they decided to attack? Our
		hero learned from the local townsfolk that some Novum cultists discovered a new
		source of power within the Oblitus Shrine deep in the Pestis Woods. They call it
		the Forgotten Schism. Ever since then, the cult of Novum has used its powers to
		gain control of the colony and eventually overthrow the Empire and reclain their
		place in the world. 
		In order to further proceed, our hero must first take over the colony's capital,
		Umbilicus, located southeast of Serena. This is where the cult's of Novum's main
		forces are gathered.
		To get there, the young hero can either travel south and fight through the Novum
		cult's troops, or journey east through the Exilium Peaks. Rumor has it that a
		legendary prophet lives deep within the mountains.
		Yet another crossroad in our hero's destiny. What will he choose?
  </Text>
  <Text id="Exilium PeaksIntro">
		Choosing the path of exile and wisdom, our hero headed through the Exilium Peaks.
		Was it the rumors of the legendary prophet that led him here, or rather was he
		hoping to find an easy way out without fighting?
		No matter the reason, the surprise on his face was without a doubt due to the
		hordes of bandits waiting for his army at the end of the road...
  </Text>
  <Text id="Exilium PeaksEnd">
		Another exhausting battle came to an end. A sad expression covered our hero's
		face.
		
		"Why are there so many bandits on this island? Is it really that hard to make an
		honest living here? So many people trying to live their life here yet the Empire
		doesn't lift a finger to help them... I'm starting to wonder if the Empire is
		not using the cult of Novum's uprising as an excuse to eradicate the colony...
		I heard a legendary prophet lives nearby. Someone so wise as to be called a
		prophet would propably be able to unveil this shadow of doubt plaguing me and
		answer my questions."
		
		Thus the hero began seeking the prophet. Will his perseverance be enough to find
		this legendary figure? Only the future will tell...
  </Text>
  <Text id="Prophet ShrineIntro">
    "I finally found it, the prophet's shrine!"
		
		As he walked into the shrine, the hero heard some mysterious chanting and saw an
		old man in a battle stance.
		
		- If it is answer you seek, defeat me in battle you shall!
		
		The hero and the prophet engaged in battle...
  </Text>
  <Text id="Prophet ShrineEnd">
    As the prophet was defeated, his words echoed throughout the shrine.
		
		- Strong you are, my wisdom you deserve. Question you need not to ask, for all
		  the answers I have. The Forgotten Schism is the key behind this whole story.
		  It is an ancient relic from times long forgotten, the initial source of strife
		  between Vetus and Novum. A similar device was found when the Empire's civil
		  war began but the cult of Vetus quickly proceeded to destroy it and hide the
		  facts from the people. It is a source of power beyond our comprehention. 
		  Learning how to master it was Novum's ambition, the change it would bring was
		  Vetus's fear. I believe another decision will fall into your hands in the near
		  future. The path you will take will change the destiny of this world, but the
		  decision is entirely up to you. Farewell young man.
			
		Before leaving, the prophet gave the hero a mysterious amulet, instructing him
		to use it in the absolute center if he ever needed help for his battle in the
		capital. The hero thanked him and proceeded towards Umbilicus.
  </Text>
  <Text id="SolutumIntro">
    This is the intro for Ancora
    the first region map.
  </Text>
  <Text id="SolutumEnd">
    This is the conclusion for Ancora
    the first region map.
  </Text>
  <Text id="AuxiliatorIntro">
    This is the intro for Ancora
    the first region map.
  </Text>
  <Text id="AuxiliatorEnd">
    This is the conclusion for Ancora
    the first region map.
  </Text>
  <Text id="UmbilicusIntro">
    This is the intro for Ancora
    the first region map.
  </Text>
  <Text id="UmbilicusEnd">
    This is the conclusion for Ancora
    the first region map.
  </Text>
  <Text id="SilendaIntro">
    This is the intro for Ancora
    the first region map.
  </Text>
  <Text id="SilendaEnd">
    This is the conclusion for Ancora
    the first region map.
  </Text>
  <Text id="Pestis WoodsIntro">
    This is the intro for Ancora
    the first region map.
  </Text>
  <Text id="Pestis WoodsEnd">
    This is the conclusion for Ancora
    the first region map.
  </Text>
  <Text id="LoyalGoodEnding">
    This is the ending you get if 
    you decide to fuck up the cult of Novum in Pestis Woods
    and you have a good alignment.
  </Text>
  <Text id="EvilGoodEnding">
    This is the ending you get if
    you decide to fuck up the cult of Novum in Pestis Woods
    and you have a bad alignment.
  </Text>
  <Text id="LoyalBadEnding">
    This is the ending you get if
    you decide to screw over your old allies in Silenda Port
    and you have a good alignment.
  </Text>
  <Text id="EvilBadEnding">
    This is the ending you get if
    you decide to screw over your old allies in Silenda Port
    and you have a bad alignment.
  </Text>
</TextList>
